My name is Nisha Bajaj and I have been associated with Aditya
Birla Sun Life Insurance for the last 22
years.
[Sangeet].
I actually believe that whatever I
am today is because of Aditya Birla Life Insurance.
Earlier, I
was just a normal housewife, then through training etc.
and my MDRT achievements kept increasing year by
year. Then I not only learned about
what can be done only for insurance,
I also got to learn a lot for my own personality development.
Initially, I was very hesitant as to
how to talk to them, how to meet them. I had
no knowledge of computers at all.
I learned everything only after joining Aditya Birla Sun Life. I get
world class training. I get
good training from famous trainers or experienced people
and I get to learn a lot of other knowledge as well.
And there is a satisfaction from within
that we are doing something for the society.
We encourage them for their protection. It is only through the
commission from my insurance that
I earned a flat and my
first car from the same commission.  I purchased a second hand
car from the same and trips do
happen and there is no limit in it, it is
in my hands as to how much business I want to do and
how much I want to earn, I go out of the country and
there I get awards in a grand level
convention, when we
share with people about receiving awards, my
respect increases, so right now I myself am
22 years old, I am going on 23 years, in between many
people invited me to
join their company, but the
atmosphere here is so homely that we
cannot even think of leaving it.